​​
Even if I search within these solemn days,​
Even if I curse the unchanging present,​
The words dancing in mid-air​
Surely cannot save you​
Music     Keina Suda​
Movie     Avogado6​
The scenery that still cannot be reached,​
And the pain that never gets warm​
Walked past each other's shoulders,​
Only hoping to go to a faraway place​
The things like "hope" you told me,​
If they are the ideals you saw in your dreams,​
No matter how cold it gets,​
I'll show you my love​
Even if I search within these solemn days,​
Even if I curse the unchanging present,​
The words dancing in mid-air​
Surely cannot save you​
Even if I shout with my worthless voice,​
The heat-bearing night will still arrive​
Even if this hand is released,​
I hope to be able to walk forward​
The words I'm unable to share with you,​
they increase every time I notice them​
Face the present and continue to change,​
I want you to keep looking at this figure​
The future you spoke of was only​
unable to be held by these hands​
No matter how you cover it up,​
Behind that smile of yours,​
You still doubt me, don't you?​
Even if it's the future of these unending days,​
Even if it's this near-unsalvageable melancholy,​
The more this finger struggles​
The more they fade away remotely​
I didn't want to know​
the color of untouchable memories​
Although you aren't here anymore,​
I still want to keep dreaming​
If the reification of misfortune attacks you,​
I want to touch it with the palm of my hand​
If the decorated words that you spit out
are for cursing someone​
Then keep your mouth shut​
Even if I search within these solemn days,​
Even if I curse the unchanging present,​
The words dancing in mid-air​
Surely cannot save you​
Even if I shout with my worthless voice,​
The heat-bearing night will still arrive​
Even if this hand is released,​
I hope to be able to walk forward​
Hopefully, without saying goodbye,​
One day, we'll meet again somewhere​