​
Haooo! HimeHina here!​
​​Haooo! HimeHina here!
This time!
We’re going to answer the questions we got in our question box,
except!
Except?
We’ll answer in rap
Answering questions​
​​Answering questions
while rapping!​
​​while rapping!
Rapping!
This pumping beat
This swinging heart
Heart, T, T...
Tick the boxes
Shiritori
I have some questions I want to ask you
Answer them while rapping as you should do
Ordinary rap can go far away
We’re doing giggle rap, HimeHina
One, two
Are you ready?​
​​Are you ready?
What is your favorite special day?
Let’s listen
to what Hime
has to say!
Alright, leave it to me, this one’s easy
Goes without saying that it’s the Hinamatsuri!
Third day of third month, festival of peaches
Wishing for little girls’ health and fitness!
Nice one
That’s a nice one
Now tell us how you like your ramen done!
Lots of types are going ‘round, so what ramen?
The one I like most would be tonkotsu, yeah
Pictures at midnight make me so hungry
Ramen, Tsukemen, Tanaka Himen!
This here
is the next
question I got for ya
What angle should a comaneci be performed at?
This is really important to me so listen close
I do a lotta cool comanecis in the Roki video,
well that’s the ideal
The sign of V is 45°
Bring your hands up, move diagonally
About those
gigglebuns you
have on your head
Do you normally tie those up yourself?
Hina does that for me at morning
Right? Hina
I do
I shake her awake in bed every time in the morning
and then tie her hair into neat gigglebuns
Now it’s your turn, Hina!
Mic check, one, okay
It’s my turn
Let’s go then
Answer me
this nice question over here
What is your English word of the year?
English is not in my zone, but anyway
If I had to pick, it be PSYCHO-PASS
Any place you go, get a free pass
※ Just wanted to say it
Being VIP sounds amazing, right?
Suzuki Hina Hinna
HinaHina
Is this a question?
Is that from Golden Kamuy?
“Hinna” means “thanks a lot” in Ainu
“Hinna” expresses gratitude in the Ainu language
So Suzuki Thanks Thanks?
It’s closer to “thanks for the food”
Uho Uho Uhohoho
KYAAI! KYAAI!
AH AH AH
Uho
Uhoho?
Uhho
Uhohoho
I’m trying to rap here, please be quiet
Sorry
“Hey, are you good at rapping?”, they ask
Go ahead and
show them
Hina-chan
OK putting my soul in these lyrics here
Making them ring in my heart Division
I am rap-Taro, born from rap
Simple rapping is
good for wrapping
Meaning unclear
Syllable overflow
Good for wrapping​
​​That didn’t make much sense, did it
What’s simple rapping?
Compare each other to animals!
We’ll say the same thing, I’m sure
One, two
Bunny!​
​​Bunny!
Miracle
Wow, we got the same
What’s your source of happiness?
Seeing that Jojimin are up and having fun
Fun!​
​​Seeing that Jojimin are up and having fun
That’s what we get lots of our happiness from
From!​
​​That’s what we get lots of our happiness from
Thank you
I’m so glad
Hina-arare
Super sweet picture time!
Huh? What?​
​​Yes, just like that, cute
Look at the camera!
Stop that~​
​​Excuse me, could you-
Yes, just like that!
What’s your favorite four-character expression?
Sessatakuma!
(※ Cultivating oneself through diligent study)
Azabu-jūban!
(※ District in Tokyo)
Just saying those sounds like you’re rapping, no?
Only sounds like it
How long can Hime stand still?
Let’s find out!
And start!
Testing
You moved!
5 seconds? That’s it?
Alright, we’re leaving the ballad behind, hitting that 200BPM!
Ballad’s over!
How’s it going? How you doing?
Fairly
Nicely
Perfectly
All day and all year having fun YO!
Who is that standing there behind you?
Nonono
Can’t take horror
Don’t say that, someone will actually show up!
Do the subscription dance at lightspeed
Tantaranta tantaranta subscribe!​
​​Tantaranta tantaranta subscribe!
Tanaka and Suzuki, subscribe YO!​
​​Tanaka and Suzuki, subscribe YO!
You’re going to die from laughing too much
We’ll laugh until our last breath!
Always happy
HimeHina channel!​
​​HimeHina channel!
It’s over!
We did it!
Our rapping power (?) is higher than ever
Hey man
Filler phrase
So yes!
Thank you for your many questions!
Thank you
We also got many that weren’t actually questions though
Right?​
​​We also got many that weren’t actually questions though
Hinna Hinna
But they got us laughing, so it’s fine
We’ll do another question corner sometime,
so please send us many more then!
Thank you!​
​​Thank you~
And now we say
Goodbye!​
​​Goodbye!
Join the unofficial ​HimeHina fanclub!​
​https://discordapp.com/invite/yusTycR
Tantaranta tantaranta sub-scri-be!
Pipii!
Tanaka and Suzuki
Sub-scri-be!
Aw yeah!