​​
​​  Translation by Hazuki​
​​  Modified by [XV]​
Little by little, the cold, incessant rain​
washed away the trace of my tears.​
Somewhere in a corner​
of the once familiar twilight sky,​
I saw someone smiling.​
I’ve grown up and without even realizing it myself,​
I’ve become able to tell more elaborate lies;​
I've experienced many pains,​
but even so,​
this ache still lingers.​
The twilight is so red,​
it makes me feel like crying;​
If it could only fade away​
your presence in my mind.​
My whole body is​
so overrun with scars left by you.​
I just...​
I can't go on anymore.​
Tell me, why I'm still​
holding onto you so tightly?​
Yet I'm wishing for you to leave​
and erase yourself from my mind?​
Your voice is becoming​
fainter and fainter​
in the engulfing red.​
I'm sure it will simply go on and on​
melting away your presence in my mind​
turning it into night.​
The red seems as if it could spill over​
and fall onto my faintly dyed fingertips.​
It’s going to take away​
your image​
inside my mind.​
The clouds are breaking apart,​
and tears are flowing from between the gaps.​
I held on tightly​
to your image inside me​
as it slowly became a blurred glow.​